You get one life. Make yours matter.
Soul on Fire is a drama film directed by Sean McNamara.
After a horrific accident leaves his body scarred, a young boy strives to live and show everyone what is possible with
the help of his family, his faith, his community, his longtime idol's kindness, and the entire city of St.
John O'Leary, played by Joel Courtney.
Jack Buck, played by William H. Macy.
Denny O'Leary, played by John Corbett.
Nurse Roy, played by DeVon Franklin.
Susan O'Leary, played by Stephanie Szostak.
Beth O'Leary, played by Masey McLain.
Soul on Fire is a 2025 American biographical drama
film about John O'Leary, a real-life St.
Louis native who survived fire burns which covered his entire body.
It is directed by Sean McNamara based on a screenplay by Gregory Poirier that adapted
O'Leary's book On Fire, The 7 Choices to Ignite a Radically Inspired Life.
The film stars Joel Courtney portraying O'Leary, John Corbett, Stéphanie
Szostak, Masey McLain, DeVon Franklin, and William H.
It was released in the United States and Canada on
October 10, 2025 by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, faith, based
on true story, burn victim, st. louis, missouri.
The tone is emotional.